Department of Women's Studies fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Speakers and lectures files, 1977 - 1991; F-63-5; 9 cm of textual records 1 photograph 1 oversize poster; Physical description: 1 photograph located in F-63-5-0-0-7 Physical description:
  - Programs of Distinction -- Lectures by distinguished visitors, vol. 2, 1977 - 1984; F-63-5-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 63-7)
  - Programs of Distinction -- Lectures by distinguished visitors (photograph of Linda M. Fedigan), vol. 3, 1977 - 1984; F-63-5-0-0-7 (Archival box - small 63-8)
  - Programs of Distinction -- proposals, 1979 - 1986; F-63-5-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 63-7)
  - Guest lecturers -- administrative, 1979 - 1982; F-63-5-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 63-7)
- Publications and posters files, 1972 - 2004; F-63-6; 3 cm of textual records 5 oversize posters
  Series consists of publications and promotional materials that have been actively collected by the SFU Archives to document the Women's Studies program and department. Records include newsletters, program information, posters, brochures, and other documents.
  The series was established by the archivist to reflect the grouping of publications and posters collected by the SFU Archives to document the Women's Studies program and department, as well as to contain oversize posters arising from other series in the fonds.
  - Brochures, newsletters and posters, vol. 1, 1972 - 2004; F-63-6-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 63-5)
  - Brochures, newsletters and posters, vol. 2, 1972 - 2004; F-63-6-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 63-5)
  - Brochures, newsletters and posters (oversize posters), vol. 3, 1972 - 2004; F-63-6-0-0-3 (Cabinet MC 40-05)
  - Oversize posters, 1991 - 2002; F-63-6-0-0-4 (Cabinet MC 40-05)
  - 20th Anniversary 1975 - 1995 Women's Studies booklet, F-63-6-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 63-5)